cédric angot soul funk you for attending
cédricangot soul致谢您参加
corn and sheikh amine press must
玉米和酋长胺新闻必须
kevin meet the room so i'll try to be my
凯文遇见房间，所以我会尽力成为我的
guest i'm going to speak about jacques
客人，我要讲雅克
attali a well known topic laughing at
附加一个众所周知的话题，嘲笑
eclipses as a mourning proposed to it
日食作为向它提出的哀悼
with the specific hangar following at
与特定的机库位于
use prospective
使用预期
what was we use up respective weiner
我们用尽了什么威纳
accor announces old is intended to open
雅高宣布将开放旧车
jacques attali source to observe lot of
雅克·阿塔利来源观察到很多
enthusiasm in the community my
我对社区的热情
personal reaction world bores me in ce2
个人反应世界让我在ce2中感到无聊
in wang haiwen our api with the
在wang haiwen我们的api与
lack of progress of the clients platform
客户平台缺乏进展
lynch in july says bat indians harold
7月的林奇说蝙蝠印第安人哈罗德
hyman than meets the eye the beats and
海曼胜过眼神
small col bones the capacity to define
小col骨的定义能力
and implement and open source
实施和开源
governance model because i think that
治理模型，因为我认为
içki governance for the standard
içki治理标准
platform
平台
except the oms and i'll try to be active
除了OMS，我会尽量保持活跃
watch this pignol jersey
观看这件皮尼奥尔球衣
writing article
写文章
dring presentation tox like to day and
像今天一样喝演示毒
getting feed backs so if you want the
得到反馈，所以如果你想
boat yum jean-françois james a work
百胜船长让·弗朗索瓦·詹姆斯（James-françois）
adroit rhein atos origin company
阿德罗特·大黄酸源公司
anatole company our origin anathos
anatole公司我们的起源anathos
company to my seller who use of
公司给我的卖家谁使用
experience in haiti so what do i do at
在海地的经验，我该怎么办
war like we build and run digital
像我们建立和运行数字化战争
platforms on behalf of the work of the
平台代表的工作
We have expanded
我们扩大了
aubert capacity to wait
奥伯特等待的能力
electronic transactions any other
电子交易其他
domain sap chazel strand door
域树汁查泽尔链门
government
政府
a baby of most style pop art of my
我最喜欢波普艺术的婴儿
career as been chara eyes band monbana
曾担任Chara Eye Band Monbana的职业
20 years with it has started with
20年的开始
the one that one longtime
那一个很久的
open tomcat resin and djiby tommy jake
打开tomcat树脂和djiby汤米杰克
moss on all kinds of platform
各种平台上的苔藓
projects seals said if hadd ndao of my
工程印章说如果我的had ndao
tho will start with retrospective
从回顾开始
know in the past is essential to look to
知道过去必不可少的
the future we will analyze at angie la
未来我们将在安吉拉进行分析
tablet everything sokol clown and yves
平板电脑一切sokol小丑和伊夫
application to 8 this specific pigment
应用于8种特定颜料
and the good work has real is
好的工作是真实的
of the jedi platform and the baseline of
绝地平台的基准和
jacques attali at will it blend what i'm
雅克·阿塔利会融合我的精神吗
in by the turbine and then we are bound
在涡轮机中，然后我们被束缚
last year and of course we will see
去年，当然我们会看到
challenge for the future we saw this is
未来的挑战，我们看到这是
my vigor of the evolution of the valley
我对山谷发展的热情
intel java platform and seven wilkes
英特尔java平台和七个wilkes
specific punk rehab jared leto so long
特定的朋克康复疗养地雷这么久
time it started with the joy times
从欢乐的时光开始
said eun sun times both men
说太阳日报两人
prehistoric times zintan was good
史前时代的津丹人很好
running not because specifications
运行不是因为规格
warden inspect first reproach starting
监狱长检查第一次责备开始
from language in isolation form of
来自语言的孤立形式
developers very targeted attacks led
开发人员针对性很强的攻击导致
to over complexity in twenty with
超过二十
jay everything is there that for which was
周杰伦一切都在那里，那是为了
the gardener as the truck of zill
园丁作为吉尔的卡车
o'll min
分钟
you know the button in 2nd single hands
你知道第二只手的按钮
agricultural gartner in response to that
农业Gartner对此做出回应
rajohnson road book frustration
拉约翰逊路书的挫败感
proposing and alternative pragmatic
求婚和务实
way to develop java enterprise
开发Java企业的方法
applications in town and eugene
在城镇和尤金的应用
pact in de community france
法国社区条约
Heatley to the creation of spring fall
希特利（Heartley）创作春季秋季
indie rock it also invited people working
独立摇滚也邀请人们一起工作
in terms of story specifications considered in
根据故事的规范考虑
working and decision to switch turcotte
工作和决定转换turcotte
France reproaches to be more pragmatic
法国责备更加务实
in facetime of work five is
面对工作，五是
of development was really taken into
真正被纳入发展
consideration
考虑
jump to today named john marston
跳到今天的名字叫约翰·马斯顿
has been otiv chief luigia borsi
一直是首席首席路易斯·博伊西
framework develops by giving qingdao
通过给青岛开发框架
founder of our night which introduces
我们夜晚的创始人介绍了
sidi aïch independent context if
sidiaïch独立情境
sidi high yield generic injection
西迪高产仿制药
injection mechanism acting as the glue
注射机制充当胶水
between the specifications and also to
规格之间也要
integrate external technology hadj
整合外部技术hadj
aïssa vonn oise and sankt-pauli
艾萨·冯·瓦兹和圣保罗
continuity with additional fitch we like
连续性和我们喜欢的舒适感
it or badge posting jason posting
它或徽章发布杰森发布
websocket supports a competitor sea to
websocket支持竞争对手
support to saint claud news programming
支持圣克劳德新闻节目
and by the way java is even was very
顺便说一句，java甚至非常
good very match release
很好，非常适合发布
so from strategic Jamaica standpoint
所以从牙买加的战略角度来看
from five to seven i was good friday
从五点到七点我是星期五
between innovation and standardization
在创新和标准化之间
time to be the place to stand or die
是时候站起来或死了
innovation which by the west jpf show
西方JPF展示的创新
orleans
奥尔良
it is solid hibernate standardization
这是可靠的冬眠标准化
cydia xdrive from the team gym
来自团队健身的cydia xdrive
bachas bin ali in french by spring match
bachas bin ali春季比赛用法语
especially vahirua the good fit for
特别是vahirua
long term project which is typically from
长期项目，通常来自
kitchen payment where we need
我们需要的厨房付款
capitalization in technical stack
技术堆栈中的大写
backward compatibility amstrong patch
向后兼容性amstrong补丁
management in particular security patch
管理特别是安全补丁
management to fail special payment card
管理层未能通过特殊付款卡
industry regulation sleep bychawa i
行业法规睡眠睡眠
was not very innovative built 3rd winnie
不是很创新的第三个小熊
reasonable choice for many enterprise
许多企业的合理选择
project
项目
tandja ys seven days of shipping
tandja是运输七天
to accelerate driven by continue this blur
加速驱动，继续这种模糊
the innovation started many years ago i
创新始于多年前
popular amazon to the concept of
流行的亚马逊概念
cloud platform for boks calling for
博克斯呼吁的云平台
better cooperation between days of death
死亡日之间的更好合作
is good practices in chaz continues this
在chaz中的良好做法继续了
displacement
移位
a sugar phrase to the codes nossik when
代码nossik的糖语短语何时
and polished persistent 6 or a
并抛光持久性6或
solution this hunting cassandra mongodb
解决这个狩猎卡桑德拉mongodb
challenging traditional cycle of
挑战传统的
smoking
抽烟
mike roux russian architect service a
mike roux俄罗斯建筑师服务有限公司
netflix body shaped to hesbaye
netflix身体形状为hesbaye
the star factors that containers
容器的明星因素
revolution France where some in
法国革命
berne and s and they come back goal
berne和s他们回来了
programming tucci concrete stability and
编程tucci混凝土的稳定性和
scalability will have cloud applications
可扩展性将拥有云应用程序
platform
平台
in club platforms and a few years is all
在俱乐部平台上，几年就是全部
the strange prove to be free
奇怪的证明是免费的
together and led to what we call
一起导致了我们所说的
and yves typical applications of the made of
和yves的典型应用
self rene revol distributed service is
自订rere分布式服务是
built in residence inn beirouthine
建于贝罗多因住宅旅馆
Czech monitoring package in diploids
二倍体捷克监测软件包
incontinence in flat club france making
扁平俱乐部法国制造中的失禁
the most of them up
他们最多
semi arid zone our languages ​​room in a
半干旱地区我们的语言室
model hands on the left no customers
模特双手放在左边没有顾客
lee the child is on the right and claude
李的孩子在右边和格斗
native applications
本机应用
harbi as mainstream even for
哈尔比甚至成为主流
traditional organization
传统组织
and what happened to that good old joy
那美好的旧时快乐发生了什么
platform in the meantime wild nothing
平台在此期间一无所有
jogging all years a speech all be
多年来慢跑演讲都是
very damaging phases of platforms
平台的破坏性很强的阶段
because manie developpers decided to
因为很多开发者决定
move away from it
远离它
twenty sixty with two initiative in
二十六岁
response to the lack of progress
对缺乏进展的反应
hte it's group the jedi war jones or
这是绝地战争琼斯或
this woman in order to we
这个女人为了我们
started to specifications
开始规范
sauzée organizes on 20 hot betty but
sauzée组织了20个热门贝蒂，但
noise trying to include will be like a
试图包含的噪音将像
asset sentheim group jazz the avengers
资产森海姆集团爵士复仇者
started the mind own fans initiative
开始了自己的粉丝倡议
to define and open specification for
定义和开放规范
java micro service in two is better
Java Micro Service一分为二比较好
hadja bahwan oracle will have like that of
hadja bahwan甲骨文将会像
new a jewel will be the map the objectives
新的宝石将成为地图的目标
west moose platform and all there
西麋平台和所有那里
is
是
his community oise enthusiastic x games
他的社区对X游戏充满热情
and the way back on the track and one year
以及回到正轨的一年
after java and web
在Java和Web之后
glassfish five fans supplementation
玻璃鱼五迷补充
what is java there is basic in bed and
什么是java，床上有基本知识，
herbal tea at leymen tuncay theate at the
莱曼·汤卡特（the lemmen）的凉茶
reminder java 6 ee it has been
提醒java 6 ee已经
released in twenty four kings or niort
释放二十四个国王或尼奥尔
after jah is even so it was necessary to
扎哈之后，所以有必要
take into newtype that jazze optional
融入爵士乐可选的新类型
complete streams of their future jamaï aït
完整的未来jamaïaït信息流
also includes the new specifications
还包括新规范
security which offers simplified
提供简化的安全性
close to the fans who questions a
靠近质疑一个
authorization mechanism in jason by which
jason中的授权机制
offers standard to pia to buy in jazz
提供pia爵士乐购买标准
classic anne jason structure and there
经典的安妮·杰森结构和那里
were very interesting update to existing
对现有的更新非常有趣
space servlet ford at 06 10 turns 2 0 in
太空小精灵福特在06 10转2 0在
second on the basis of e-coli jamai aït was
基于e-coli jamaiaït的第二名是
very good restart of the platform
很好的重启平台
nothing rivoli ringtone to nothing really
没什么rivoli铃声什么都没有
claude native enjoy it was clearly
克劳德本地人享受这显然是
present will be like a fridge back to
现在就像冰箱一样
the road map in intermediate zone step
中间区步骤中的路线图
the target of finanza vanina the
Finanza Vanina的目标
problem is that jazz hainan azoumana yes
问题是爵士hainan azoumana是
the error exists a job is has been
错误存在，工作已经
released a mid what i call turbo en
发布了我称之为Turbo En的中段
zone be fast after twenty years of
经过20年的发展
stability
稳定性
everything changes a smart want it
一切都会变聪明
do they know and august
他们知道和八月
oracle announces it in time to stop the
甲骨文及时宣布停止
development of giants or open source it
巨头发展还是开源
me august and in the running september oracle
我八月，并在运行的九月甲骨文
announces newbury disruptive guidance for
宣布纽伯里（Newbury）破坏性指南
java 6 standard java edition with two
Java 6标准Java版有两个
feature willis period and one long term
特征威利斯时期和一个长期
support every you so this is changing
支持大家，这正在改变
for the roll java ecosystems mi
适用于Java生态系统mi
september there eclipse foundation was
九月的月食基础是
chosen java job here
在这里选择了Java工作
nine inch allah
九寸真主
same time at 9th September this top level
9月9日同一时间
eclipse enterprise ford java project was
Eclipse Enterprise Ford Java项目原为
created to host the future of jah is so
创建来承载贾哈的未来是如此
everything changes in fanti three days
三天后一切都变了
to date the tos 10 and users of
迄今为止，tos 10和用户
technology in the state of
技术状态
interrogations
审讯
what's going where we go is offered to
我们要去的地方
I went to
我去了
share are concerned are here we in
分享关注我们在这里
are expectations and in mind of the
是期望，并牢记
job jakarta platform somail phase
雅加达工作平台somail阶段
about was about the replacement of
大约是关于更换
the day 6 tracks java community process
第6天跟踪Java社区过程
except years jessy pi stoll birds
除年份杰西·皮斯托尔鸟
authority and bolt or define jabba stand
权力和螺栓或定义贾巴立场
ans andy eclipse foundation is not stand
安迪斯日蚀基金会不成立
up boli and open source herbal tea
博利和开源凉茶
organizations it is even to define open
组织甚至定义开放
specification boat leader adoption d
规格船长采用d
a district alternates them into standaard
一个地区使他们成为标准
so what will make and open specification
那么什么将使规范开放
under the auspices of eclipse better
在日食的主持下更好
than any existing solution will be
比任何现有解决方案都要
wanted in it will be
想要的会是
it is not interested
它不感兴趣
easy question in darwin note signal in
达尔文笔记信号中的一个简单问题
renaming ourselves are positive
重命名自己是积极的
indicators force
指标力
let's see what is exactly the clip
让我们看看到底是什么片段
foundation a huge pile half a hundred to
基础一大堆一百
jakarta i
雅加达
my hand standing
我的手站着
gold eclipse oise limited to decide if i
金蚀瓦兹有限公司决定我是否
like many people i think what in
像许多人一样，我认为
reality eclipse of the world
世界的现实蚀
he wanted project spread across seven
他希望项目分布在七个
technical tracks adictiz strongly
技术跟踪adictiz强烈
supported backed by sponsored by
由...赞助
sweet
甜美
one important to spect its core value in
重要的是要看清其核心价值
neutrality sellers
中立卖家
so to better ap the old zoo
为了更好地利用旧动物园
diversityinc eclipse project leash
日食项目皮带
help focus home for the heavy forget
帮助重返家园的人们忘记
eclipse enterprise ford java you already
Eclipse Enterprise Ford Java您已经
know it it is a high level project
知道这是一个高水平的项目
future of the way it is as many the
未来的方式
form approaches dirty dancing the unknown
形式接近脏舞未知
project is so many lives many lives of
项目是如此多的生命
dildos to binh chanh steria my profile
假阳具到平昌蒂斯特我的个人资料
started in twenty six
开始于二十六
has become
已经成为
an eclipse project open jean hine it in
eclipse project open jean在其中
ibm fat ibm technology it is openjdk
ibm fat ibm技术是openjdk
compliance it is and alternative to zero
它是合规的，可以替代零
this vote indicates deliverance very good
这次投票表明解救非常好
performance in terms of start up
在启动方面的表现
memory any prince all attributes in
存储任何王子的所有属性
importance in cloud platform vertix in
在云平台vertix中的重要性
the known to the kit to develop
套件开发已知的
he taunts applications it is led by
他嘲笑它领导的应用程序
red hat in jeans as she and
戴着牛仔裤的红色帽子，因为她和
geoffrey rush to facilitate our cycles
杰弗里（Geoffrey）急于促进我们的周期
integration so so this file examples we
集成，所以这个文件示例我们
-have
- 具备
the author various it is to project
作者各种各样的计划
related to open final specification
与公开的最终规范有关
project in the 3rd round help beats note
第3轮项目帮助胜过笔记
fully controlled by commercial compagnie
由商业公司完全控制
so clearly eclipse isogood flat is to
很明显，日食等距平坦是
define open specification tell him
定义开放规范告诉他
forgotten by the industry so this
因此被业界所遗忘
is good for it my second is about
对我有好处，我的第二个是关于
good governance of the ring twenty years
善治之戒二十年
the day is hippies java community
今天是嬉皮士java社区
process management will have to live there
流程管理必须住在那儿
north of technologies as customs very
作为海关的技术北方
good job in that matters
在那件事上做得好
specifications was made in the form of
规格以
jihad java specification requests with
圣战Java规范要求
the dedicated expert group
专门的专家组
leading specifications what we will define
领先的规格我们将定义什么
bookstores barnes documentation
书店barnes文档
will remain supplementation technology
将保持补充技术
compatibility kit and following will
兼容性套件及以下内容
define lifecycle initiation to find your
定义生命周期启动以找到您的
email is so this model has been denied
电子邮件，因此该模型已被拒绝
platform to last twenty years built you have
过去二十年建造的平台
not been and bolt or coop with rich and
没有和螺栓或合作与丰富和
pay off changed the world we need to day
回报改变了我们今天需要的世界
we still need strong government bat
我们仍然需要强大的政府力量
trang is not enough
特朗是不够的
we also need speed to facilitate the
我们还需要速度来促进
integration of innovation a new
融合创新
technology and the right man at the
技术和合适的人
right country so so what is the model the
正确的国家，那么模型是什么
new model offers by sleep foundation
睡眠基金会提供的新模式
and you want it is jazz hybrid jakarta
而你想要的是爵士混合雅加达
blue will be responsible of the
蓝色将负责
governance managing the brown
治理布朗
name this steering committee and the
命名这个指导委员会并
specifications process specifications
规格工艺规格
gilbert hanna standard implementation
吉尔伯特·汉娜（Gilbert Hanna）标准实施
open source project there will be no
开源项目将没有
expert group our leading specifications
专家组我们领先的规格
exclusive vip ownership rings at the
VIP专属所有权在
rings the reminder luigi cipi
敲响提醒luigi cipi
alpilles intellectual property in
阿尔皮尔斯知识产权
wazi specifications exclusive to
wazi规格专有
the archipelago of leader saw specifications
领袖群岛的锯规格
6 is no more choo
6没有更多的选择
erwin be our implementation references
erwin是我们的实施参考
not say will be at least one compatible
不说会兼容至少一种
opensourcing lamentations louise
开放源码感叹路易丝
benedito validate to specifications
benedito验证规格
access to tea sic and will be free
免费使用茶园
with the self certification mechanism
具有自我认证机制
this is also been changed because
这也已更改，因为
preview 6 accessing ticket oise
预览6访问门票瓦兹
expensive is objecting to legal
昂贵是反对法律
constraint complete if goalkeeper france
如果守门员法国完成约束
andy kaufman 6 our all this use to get
安迪·考夫曼6我们所有的这些使用
certified implementation
认证实施
so this process it assumes to be more to
因此，此过程假定更多
giles
贾尔斯
and for me it remains 'challenges'
对我来说，它仍然是“挑战”
clearly execution oxis process will be
显然执行oxis程序将
will be who was all the rage of the
将是谁的所有愤怒
platform we say devil is in the
我们说恶魔在平台上
details socli and iso challenge
详细介绍socli和iso挑战
myford is about birds burning jakarta
迈福德是关于烧雅加达的鸟类
into you close native platform as
进入您封闭的本机平台
mansion jamai has the baseline is not a
豪宅jamai的基线不是
says state of the ant referring cognitive
说蚂蚁指的是认知状态
applications what does it mean to be
应用程序意味着什么
good software claude citizens hitwise
优秀的软件称呼公民
characteristic servers hatay a
特色服务器讨厌一个
by the way said fine fruit category a
顺便说一句好水果
says ok solution flights or hercules
说可以解决方案飞行或大力神
berne and s is king
伯恩和s是国王
we need service registry in discovery
我们需要发现中的服务注册表
traffic management including routing
流量管理，包括路由
load balancing at the run time flights
运行时的负载平衡
regarding the givers mendy application
关于送礼者的申请
we need fast start up and love
我们需要快速启动和爱
footprint and fortunate fortunati de
足迹和幸运的幸运
jabba ecosystems he locks early
他早期锁定的贾巴生态系统
regarding regarding the witch project
关于女巫项目
that has opened in raised m double
在加高的m double中打开的
lightweight jump a modular
轻量级跳模块化
server applications that jazz open
爵士乐打开的服务器应用程序
liberty sow clearly now in the right
自由现在明显地播在右边
direction regarding the mypower
关于力量的方向
profile set of additional
附加配置文件集
characteristics are distributed
特征分布
architecture including external
包括外部架构
configuration
组态
buntin monitoring al sheikh
班廷监测基地
we have many distributed service is we
我们有很多分布式服务是
know we need absolutely to know how it
知道我们绝对需要知道如何
shine is what is it distributed status
发光是什么它的分布状态
racing
赛跑
self documented apis eyes a security
自我记录的api着眼安全
between service
服务之间
so let's have a look at the crow
让我们来看看乌鸦
look-alike initiative started in twenty
相似的倡议始于二十
sixtine
sixtine
with minimalist released based in three
极简主义的发布基于三个
djamaï specifications i'm a stadium
djamaï规范我是体育场
mythical old time 's up manage to deliver
神话般的旧时光设法实现
6 release is under five implementation
6发布正在五个实施中
it's in line at volleyball
在排球比赛中排队
implementation among them open liberty
实行开放自由
fanta he bows to the iedom baya has been
幻想他向伊多姆拜亚鞠躬
strafing at tommy haas race
参加汤米哈斯（Tommy Haas）比赛
under my mind is very interesting
在我心中很有趣
regarding jakarta efforts to reason
关于雅加达的推理努力
it is both demonstrator in nanning
都是南宁的示威者
better and iso demonstrator because it
更好和等示威者，因为它
has monsters haiti now and open
现在有怪物海地开放
specification can work under the
规格可以在
auspices
主持
gold eclipse said iz demonstrator
月蚀说iz示威者
because buy co inc better be caused by
因为buy co inc最好是由
construction
施工
jacques attali he jamaican planes and
雅克·阿塔利和牙买加的飞机
all its fischer aridi to be invited into
所有其Fischer aridi都将被邀请加入
jakarta yi so
雅加达宜
jakarta y into cognitive applications
雅加达进入认知应用
clown and yves platform fate i will
小丑和伊夫平台命运我会
consists in in the thing
包含在事物中
michael profile teachers elite
迈克尔个人资料教师精英
everything is put back night tokheim mesh
一切都回到夜晚托克海姆网
touching the wish list staff for the
触摸愿望清单工作人员
stock funds for coming
即将到来的股票资金
distinction platform improvement
区分平台改进
government modernization this
政府现代化
government dave atention adoption
政府敢于注意采纳
about platform improvement and
关于平台改进和
sing it is time to convert geely geely
唱歌是时候转换吉利吉利
jaïbi nsydia of armenia overlapping
亚美尼亚的贾伊比·纳西迪亚（JaïbiNsydia）重叠
ambiguity between them and it's very
他们之间的模棱两可
difficulty for newcomers to understand
新移民很难理解
why the differences we also need modules
为什么我们也需要模块的差异
to happy days implantation that we can
到快乐的日子，我们可以
use at will kill you consists of twin
随意使用会杀死你的双胞胎
wizo dependency y of mussels
贻贝的维佐依赖性
platform in times of modernization
现代化时代的平台
between beyond mike at service is we
我们之间超越麦克的服务是
need no 6 kw it seems to jane also that
不需要6千瓦，似乎也简
she's bingtuan the foundation of new
她为新人打基础
specifications in that matters this is a
在这方面的规范，这是一个
good news high single so it is important
好消息，高单所以很重要
to integrate raft ul zapped free l
集成筏ul zapped free l
is complementary alternative and
是互补的选择
crowd tourists
人群游客
to pia it's very interesting highwood
皮亚琴非常有趣
likes to see something like delta
喜欢看类似三角洲的东西
spygate from Haiti included in the light
来自海地的间谍门
from two sink rifai jpeg jpeg use in
从两个水槽rifai jpeg jpeg中使用
terms of governance eyes in shale
页岩中的治理术语
hawn
霍恩
one respects this statement this execution of
一个人尊重这一说法的执行
the customer process specifications says
客户流程规范说
it will be doing nexium allthings
它会做所有事情
actors mom michael profile anne
演员妈妈迈克尔简介anne
jakarta i could be separate haiti
雅加达我可能是单独的海地
project because they would have it
项目，因为他们会拥有它
offers mourning for trabzon lifecycle
为特拉布宗生命周期提供哀悼
jump in shares ora i think that keeping
跳入股票ora我认为保持
versed by right is meaningful would like
精通正确是有意义的
jakarta i to be comply in tweed i have
雅加达我要遵守我的花呢
six languages ​​term supports lighting
六种语言术语支持照明
jakarta is special production at
雅加达是在
feedback compatible with the way
反馈方式兼容
i see it which will remain mainstream
我认为它将继续成为主流
for law and clearly
为法律而明确
newlands term supports based on july 6
基于7月6日的纽兰特条款支持
eleven
十一
and we need consistent haye if anne luz
如果安妮·卢兹（Ann Luz），我们需要一致的哈耶
coupling with cloud platform
与云平台耦合
particular berne was this docker is
特别伯恩是这个码头工人是
you i'm in our direct technical
你我在我们的直接技术领域
dependence is from jacques attali all
依赖来自雅克·阿塔利
club platforms and also think that
俱乐部平台，也认为
means when you are strong mass be done
意味着当你强大时
to game developpers atention and
对游戏开发者的关注和
adoption because customers read focus of
采纳，因为客户阅读了
developers is now in platform clubs
开发人员现在在平台俱乐部
and in particular mastering berne was
特别是掌握伯恩是
what a docker
什么码头工人
hall berry little room for news
霍尔贝里新闻的余地很小
specifications well
规格好
established software stacks at chaz
在chaz建立成熟的软件堆栈
node.js in sprint cloud
sprint云中的node.js
so we need to heaven we need
所以我们需要天堂
to have angel eyes and to big event bat 8
拥有天使的眼睛和大型赛事蝙蝠8
local evangelism nitoo is organizing there
当地的布道士nitoo正在组织那里
innova cities in the green it up hansson
绿色创新的汉诺威城市汉森
adonix roles time and billing me it's
adonix角色时间并向我收费
not easily title challenge to speak
不容易说出标题挑战
jakarta and a michael profile of course
雅加达和迈克尔当然的个人资料
we need is i intuitive to dobson
我们需要的是我对多布森的直觉
yes project start things like spring
是的，项目开始像春天
initializes hours in the national register
初始化国家寄存器中的小时
youth happy to see jeepster with
青年高兴地看到吉普车与
the back with back and the boys mike
背部与背部和男孩迈克
love profile in jakarta and we need is
喜欢雅加达的个人资料，我们需要的是
love testing customers read here this domain
喜欢测试的客户请在此处阅读此域
where el djazaïr of eisenstein a half in
艾森斯坦的djazaïr有一半在
important project a mesh company
网格公司的重要项目
decided siding to move away from jamaica
决定退出牙买加
because of that we need lightweight
因此，我们需要轻量化
highwood ivan say in visible application
海伍德·伊凡（vanwood ivan）在可见的应用程序中说
server
服务器
and we are in the right direction think
我们朝着正确的方向思考
of course we need seamless integration
当然我们需要无缝集成
risk or doctor bernet because this
风险或医生bernet，因为这
is where developers are waiting sean
开发人员正在等待肖恩的地方
hayes and eastwei so we need to play in
海斯和伊斯特维，所以我们需要参加
out of simple dresses at this developer
从这个开发人员的简单着装
soa concludes johnny jakarta giovanni
soa总结johnny jakarta giovanni
Easter Monday
复活节星期一
it has future promise widjane michael
它有未来的希望widjane michael
profile at space the well being of any
在太空中的轮廓
new beaters
新打手
a monsters and eclipses
怪物和蚀
in the place to be to define
在要定义的地方
open specification ready to be teens
开放规范准备成年
small bay and industries made in
小海湾及其制造的工业
action will be decisive with two men
两个人的决定性行动
challenge
挑战
once again the proper execution to
再次正确执行
specifications process i'm sorry twin
规范过程，对不起，双胞胎
sisters battle think it will be who in
姐妹战斗认为它将是谁
sheep very important challenge
绵羊非常重要的挑战
we will be getting atention developers
我们将吸引注意力开发人员
in adoption soaz users weekends
周末使用户获得普及
parts of the story of france
法国故事的一部分
1 date bin saeed al things that hockey
1日期斌说曲棍球
maybe we are ready for the twenty years
也许我们已经为二十年做好了准备
montano
蒙塔诺